Manorma Sharma

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Delhi, 110041 DL 851-289-3890 mannuu0501@gmail.com **LinkedIn:** linkedin.com/in/manorma-

sharma

SUMMARY

Expert in developing Responsive & Interactive websites | BCA Graduate | 2.5 years of experience in Web Development | Sound understanding of React js, Node js, Python, HTML5, SASS, Bootstrap 5, Wordpress | Capable of performance tuning, Testing and Deployment on live site.

WORK HISTORY

Hackerearth - Web UI Developer

Banglore, Karnataka 05/2022 - 06/2023

Responsibilities

- Templates customization of opensource and licensing web applications like (WordPress)
- Worked on in-house projects
- Responsible for Performance tuning of the website, Manage the SEO improvements, Web Core vitals.
- Responsible for Headless CMS using Wordpress with React
- Learned technologies: Basics of Azure, CI/CD Setup, React Js, Node js, ES6, WebPack, WordPress Template customization, Canvas JS.

Oceanic Studio - Front-End Developer

Delhi, Delhi 11/2020 - 04/2022

Responsibilities

- Responsible for delivery of assigned module, components or phases of project
- Templates customization of opensource and licensing web applications like (WordPress, Opencart etc.)
- Gather requirements by working closely with coordinate manager.
- Communicate conceptual ideas and design effectively in crossfunctional product development team.
- Developed UI screens using CSS, JavaScript for validations, and jQuery for animations Frontend and Backend of Projects.
- Designing website layouts, CSS animation.
- Create presentation for client to showcase deliveries and innovations.
- Code review and knowledge sharing sessions with peers and support them in HTML structuring
- Decision making to solve any given problem statement
- Learned technologies like Sass, Gulp, Bitbucket, PHP.

SKILLS

HTML, Scsss, Javascript

Bootstrap 5

Wordpress

ECMAScript

Photoshop, Figma

Javascript, Python

Github, Bitbucket, Jira

Gulp, Jquery

Webpack, Json

React js, Node js, Express js

Basic Azure, CI/CD setup

AWARDS

• Kudos Award from Hackerearth

CERTIFICATES

Certificate in "HTML 5 & CSS 3" from Udemy

Certificate in "Bootstrap" from Udemy

EDUCATION

01/2019 - 06/2022

Indra Gandhi National Open University Delhi, DL

• Bachelor of Computer Application (Graduation)

01/2015 - 04/2016

Central Board of Secondary Education, Delhi

Delhi, DL

• Intermediate (12th)

01/2013 - 04/2014

Central Board of Secondary Education, Delhi

Delhi, DL

• High School (10th)

INTERESTS

Working on IOT projects (eg: Raspberry Pi, Arduino, Node MCU)

Net Surfing for Innovation, Ideas and Learning

Book Reading, Sketching

Certificate in "Python" from Besant Technology, Banglore

Certificate in "Essential Sass Training" from LinkedIn

Certificate in "Essential GitHub Training" from LinkedIn